http://www.portset.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Assistive technology for physically disabled and visually impaired
Privacy Policy
At Portset Systems Ltd guarantee our commitment to respecting and protecting your online privacy.
This includes your need and your right to know what we do with the personal information you share with us. It also guides our company’s policies regarding the management of this data, including how the information is collected, processed, and for what purposes.
“Portset Systems”: refers to the web pages. By accessing this website you are consenting to the way information is collected and used, as described within this Privacy Policy.
In return, Portset Systems gives the commitment that we will use the personal data you provide only in ways that are compatible with the following Privacy Policy.
The collection of information
Every time you log on to our website your IP (Internet Protocol) address registers on our servers. Your IP address reveals no information other than the number assigned to you. We do not use this technology to get any personal data against your knowledge or free will (i.e., automatically recording e-mail addresses of visitors). Nor do we use it for any purpose other than to help us monitor traffic on our website, or (in case of criminal activity or misuse of our information) to cooperate with law enforcement.
Cookies
We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance.
The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.)
First Party Cookies
These are cookies that are set by this website directly.
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information.We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Third Party Cookies
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook and Google+. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.
You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at office1@portset.co.uk.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to office1@portset.co.uk.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
We take your privacy very seriously and comply with the recent UK and EU law on handling cookies and provide (you) the user with means to remove such cookies or prevent your computer from accepting them in the future.
Browser specific instructions to block and remove cookies
Internet Explorer
http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955
Firefox
http://support.mozilla.org/en–US/kb/Cookies
Google Chrome
http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647
Opera
http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/
Safari
http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?artnum=32467
Safari iOS
http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677
Android
http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022
Blackberry
Turnoffcookiesinthebrowser
Windows Phone
Changingprivacyandotherbrowsersettings
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of then you may contact us >here
About us Portset Systems Ltd has been engaged in the creation, design and production of devices and services for the visually impaired and physically disabled for some 30 years.
Principally in the area of visually impairment Portset has provided novel products to users in both the UK as well as Internationally.
Award winning products include:
Refurbished Portset Document Reader.
Portset Digital Media Centre
Braille Keyboard | BrailleKey G0/1, G2, UEB & SH
iPad, iPhone, Android tablet or phone Wheelchair or Scooter USB Auto Charger
Text Reader for Visually Impaired
We offer from time to time refurbished products which when available will be shown below.
We offer from time to time refurbished products which when available will be shown below.
Text Reader for Visually Impaired
iPad, iPhone, Android tablet or phone Wheelchair or Scooter USB Auto Charger
Braille Keyboard | BrailleKey G0/1, G2, UEB & SH
Portset Digital Media Centre
Refurbished Portset Document Reader.
Refurbished Portset Document Reader.
Portset Digital Media Centre
Braille Keyboard | BrailleKey G0/1, G2, UEB & SH
iPad, iPhone, Android tablet or phone Wheelchair or Scooter USB Auto Charger
Text Reader for Visually Impaired
We offer from time to time refurbished products which when available will be shown below.
Portset Systems Ltd. All rights reserved.
Portset and KeySpeak are registered trade marks of Portset Systems Ltd.
· Sitemap · Privacy Policy
Acknowledgments: Pictures - Giles Watson
